好了 我查过了
Okay, okay, I checked.
我们有伯爵茶 英式早餐茶 肉桂茶
We have Earl Grey, English Breakfast, Cinnamon Stick
菊花茶 薄荷茶 黑莓茶
Chamomile, Mint Medley, Blackberry and...
等等 还有一种 柠檬花草茶
Oh, wait, there's one more, Lemon Soother.
点茶的人不是你 对不对
You're not the guy that asked for the tea, are you?
好吧
Okay.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第19集
猴子出逃 The One Where the Monkey Gets Away
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：小龟快快跑
瑞秋葛林 有你的信
Mail call. Rachel Green, bunk seven.
谢谢
Thank you.
酷 免费咖啡试饮包
Oh, cool. A free sample of coffee.
真好 不然哪儿还有免费的咖啡喝
Oh, good, because where else would we get any?
对哦
Oh, right.
呵 这可好了      那是什么
Oh, great.         What is it?
乡村俱乐部的新闻通告
Country club newsletter.
我妈为了激励我 专门送这种订婚消息来
My mother sends me the engagement notices for inspiration.
噢 天啊
Oh my God!
噢 天啊 是巴瑞和敏蒂
Oh my God! It's Barry and Mindy.
巴瑞 你差点就      我差点就
Barry, who you almost...        Barry, who I almost...
敏蒂 你的伴娘      敏蒂 我的伴娘
Mindy, your maid of...        Mindy, my maid of...
那就是敏蒂
That's Mindy?
哇 好漂亮
Wow, she is pretty.
她很幸运
Lucky...
有你这样的朋友
to have had a friend like you.
马塞尔 把饭拿过来给我 快点
Marcel, bring me the rice! come on!
把饭拿过来 快点
Bring me the rice. Come on!
好孩子 好孩子 过来 拿饭给我
Good boy. Good bye. Come here, give me the rice.
谢谢你 真乖
Thank you. Good boy.
我看他总算能弄清
Well I see, he's mastered the difference between
"拿来"跟"尿在"的分别了
"bring me the" and "pee in the".
"拿来"和 瑞秋
"Bring me the" and Rach?
什么事      嗨
What?         Hi.
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
我真傻
Oh, this is so stupid.
是我甩掉巴瑞的 不是吗      嗯
I mean, I gave Barry up, right?        Hmm.
我应该为他们感到高兴
I should be happy for them.
我的确为他们感到高兴
I am. I'm happy for them.
真的吗      假的
Really?        No.
我想 要是我身边有了别人 感觉就不一样了
Oh, oh, I guess it would be different If I were with somebody.
喔 你不是说过 不要再谈恋爱了
Whoa, what, what happened to "Forget relationships".
不再和男人在一起 你的禁欲令呢
"I'm done with men"? The whole penis embargo?
我也说不清
Oh, I don't know.
我想应该不是说完全不要男人
I guess it's not about no guys.
而是要找到对的男人 你明白吗      嗯
It's about the right guy, you know?        Hmm.
跟巴瑞在一起
I mean with Barry
感觉很安全自在 但是没有激情
it was safe and it was easy, but there was no heat.
跟巴洛就只有激情
You know, with Paolo, that's all there was, was heat.
就是那种野兽般原始的性爱
And I mean, it was just this raw animal sexual...
好了 好了 我明白了
Right, right. I got it.
我看在眼里
I was there.
你觉得有没有可能两者兼有
I mean, do you think you can ever have both?
就是那种 是知己
You know, someone who's like your best friend
同时又能让你激情荡漾的人
but then also can make your toes curl.
了解 了解
Yes, yes.
真的 我完全了解
Yes. Yes I do. I really do.
其实 好玩的是
In fact, it's funny.
通常你认为那个不会让你
Very often, someone who you wouldn't think could.
激情荡漾的人
curl your toes...
可能就是那个      嗨
might just be the one who...        Hi!
被打断了 嗨
gets interrupted. Hi!
嘿 电影好看吗
Hey guys, how was the movie?
太棒了      非常好看
Oh, so wonderful.         Oh, it was so good.
烂到爆      只有女生才会去看
Suck fest.         Total chick flick.
很抱歉那不是那种
I'm sorry it wasn't one of those movies
有枪有炮
with like, you know, like guns and bombs...
或是巴士开超快的电影
and like buses going really fast.
喂 我喜欢的电影 不一定要有暴力
Hey, I don't need violence to enjoy a movie.
只要有一些裸露镜头就够了
Just so long as there's a little nudity.
有裸露镜头啊      我是说女性的裸露镜头
There was nudity.        I meant female nudity.
我可不想看路格兰特的前戏
All right, I don't need to see Lou Grant frolicking.
休 休・格兰特
Hugh, Hugh Grant.
好了 我该走了
All right, I've got to go.
过来 马塞尔 过来
Come on, Marcel. Come on.
我们要去洗澡
Yeah, we're gonna go take a bath.
对不对 对啊 我们要洗澡哦 好不好
Yes, we are, aren't we? Yes, we are.
他们仍然只是朋友 对吧
They're still just friends, right?
我们明天见
And I will see you tomorrow.
没错 明天你要来瑞秋阿姨这边待一天 对不对
That's right. You're gonna spend tomorrow at Aunt Rachel's, aren't you?
等一下 等一下 摩妮卡阿姨有没有权利说话
Hang on, hang on. Does Aunt Monica get a say in this?
拜托啦 摩妮卡阿姨 好不好
Please, Aunt Monica, please?
拜托 放轻松 明天你根本就不在
Oh, unclench, you're not even gonna be here.
真不敢相信我们居然在讨论这种事
I can not believe we're even having this discussion.
同意 我也不敢相信
I agree. I'm like in disbelief.
你不觉得 如果你跟瑞秋能在一起
I mean, don't you think, if things were gonna happen with Rachel,
你们早就在一起了
they would've happened already?
我告诉你们 她说她想要跟
I'm telling you, she said she's looking for a relationship
像我这样的人谈恋爱
with someone exactly like me.
她真的这么说
She really said that?
"像我这样的" 是我自己加的
Well, I added the "exactly like me" part.
但是她说她在找个好男人
But she said she's looking for someone.
好男人今晚就会出现
And someone is gonna be there tonight.
今晚 你是说真的
"Tonight" tonight?
我想这一定会很完美
Well, I think it's perfect, you know?
只有我们两个
It's just gonna be the two of us.
她整天都在照顾我的猴子
She spent all day taking care of my monkey.
我都不记得上次有女生
I can't remember the last time I got a girl
照顾我的猴子是什么时候的事了
to take care of my monkey.
反正 我想下班后
Anyway, you know, I figured after work
我去买一瓶酒
I'd go pick up a bottle of wine.
然后过去向她求爱
Go over there and try to woo her.
你知道你应该怎么做吗
Hey, you know what you should do?
你应该带她回到19世纪末
You should take her back to the 1890s
当时还有人使用那种字眼
when that phrase was last used.
如果你坚持下去
If you keep this up, honey
不到周末 你和那个浑蛋就一起玩完了
I swear you'll be finished with this sucker by the end of the week.
那个围着羽绒围巾的是法兰西斯医生
Now, now the one in the feathered boa, that's Dr. Francis.
她以前是个男人
Now, she used to be a man.
你看 那是瑞文 我们讨厌她
Okay, oh look. See now there's Raven. We hate her.
很高兴她快死了
We're glad she's dying.
然后 怎么了 马塞尔
And then What? What? Marcel!
你在玩摩妮卡的鞋子吗
Are you playing with Monica's shoes?
你知道你不可以
You know you're not supposed to...
哇喔
Whao!
马塞尔 你是不是在鞋子里大便了
Marcel, did you poo in the shoe?
马塞尔 坏猴子 噢
Oh, Marcel. Bad monkey. Oh!
天啊
Oh, God!
噢
Oh!
抱歉 巴瑞
Sorry, Barry.
一点祝贺你订婚的小礼物
A little engagement gift.
你的礼物清单上肯定没有这个
I'm sure you didn't register for that.
谁死了 谁死了
Who died? Who died?
把他翻过来 快点 把他翻过来 噢
Roll him over. Oh, come on, roll him over！ Oh!
我们知道那不是德柯斯特 对不对 马塞尔 因为
Well, we know it wasn't Dexter, right? Marcel? Because...
马塞尔 马塞尔 马...
Marcel? Marcel? Marc...
你怎么可能把他弄丢了
How could you lose him?
不知道 我也不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
我们在看电视
We were watching TV.
然后他在摩妮卡的鞋子里大便
And then he pooped in Monica's shoe.
等等 他在我的鞋子里大便 哪一只
Wait. He pooped in my shoe? Which one?
不知道 左脚那一只
I don't know. The left one.
哪一双
Which ones?
就是那双你认为百搭的笨重老土的鞋
Oh, those little clunky Amish things you think go with everything.
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
为什么空气中充满了负面情绪
Whoa, oh! Why is the air in here so negative?
瑞秋把马塞尔弄丢了      噢 不会吧 怎么弄的
Rachel lost Marcel.         Oh, no. How?
他在我的鞋子里大便
He pooped in my shoe.
哪一只?
Which one?
就是我常穿的那双可爱的黑鞋
Those cute little black ones I wear all the time.
不是 是哪一只
No, which one?
右脚还是左脚
The right or left?
因为左脚的话代表幸运
Because the left one is lucky.
拜托 我们该怎么办 我们该怎么办
Come on, you guys. What're we gonna do? What're we gonna do?
好吧 好吧 假如你是一只猴子
All right, all right, all right. You're a monkey.
在城市里走失了
You're loose in the city.
你会去哪里
Where do you go?
这是他第一次出门
Okay, it's his first time out.
所以他可能会去一些观光景点
So he's probably gonna want to do some of the touristy things.
我去百老汇那边找 你们去俄国茶坊找
I'll go to Cats. You go to the Russian Tea Room.
去 死 吧
Oh, my God!
拜托你们
Come on, you guys.
他马上就会回来 他会杀了我的
He's gonna be home any minute. He's gonna kill me.
我们先从这栋房子开始
Okay, we start with the building.
你们去1楼和2楼找
You guys take the first and second floor.
菲比跟我去3楼跟4楼
Phoebe and I will take third and fourth.
那我怎么办 我要做什么
Whoa, whoa, what am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?
好 你留在这里等电话
Okay, you stay here and just wait by the phone.
在我的鞋子里喷清洁剂 等罗斯回来杀你
Spray Lysol in my shoe and wait for Ross to kill you.
有人想要跟我换吗
Does anybody want to trade?
你们想干什么
What do you want?
黑考斯先生 我们朋友的猴子走丢了 你有没有看到
Mr. Heckles, our friend lost a monkey. Have you seen it?
我放了一个松饼在外头 是不是你们拿走的
I left a Belgian waffle out here. Did you take it?
不是
No.
你为什么会把松饼放在走廊里
Why would you leave your Belgian waffle in the hall?
我还不想吃
I wasn't ready for it.
猴子 你有没有看到一只猴子
The monkey, have you seen a monkey?
我见过主持人瑞吉斯一次
I saw Regis Philbin once.
谢谢你 黑考斯先生
Thank you, Mr. Heckles.
你们欠我一个松饼
You owe me a waffle.
他是一只白脸的黑色僧帽猴...
Okay, he's a black capuchin monkey with a white face...
加俄式调味汁 外加腌黄瓜
with Russian dressing and pickles on the side.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
嗨      嘿 今天还可以吧
Hi!           Hey. How did it go today?
噢 好极了 非常顺利      好
Oh, great. It went great. Really great.        Yeah.
嘿 你带酒来了      对啊
Hey, is that wine?         Yeah. Yeah.
要喝一些吗
You, want some?
噢 我很想喝      好的
Oh, I would love some.         Yeah.
这样好了 这样好了
But you know what? You know what?
我们不要在这里喝
Let's not drink it here.
我突然想疯一下 你想不想去纽瓦克
I'm feeling kind of crazy. Do you want to go to Newark?
好 好啊
Okay. Yeah.
我们当然可以去
We could do that.
但在去东北部谋杀案的首府之前
But before we head off to the murder capital of the Northeast
我想先跟你谈一件事
I was kinda wanting to run something by you.
你知道我们先前谈过的
You know how we were, you know, talking before.
有关恋爱之类的话题
About relationships and stuff, well...
噢 天啊 罗斯 我不能这么做
Oh God, Ross, I cannot do this.
好吧 迅速而痛苦
Okay, quick and painful.
噢 天啊
Oh God!
好吧 好吧 好吧
Okay, all right. All right, okay.
罗斯 请不要恨我
Ross, please don't hate me.
噢 怎么了 怎么了
Oh what? What? What?
马塞尔他
You know Marcel?
怎么了
Yeah?
嗯 我好像把他弄丢了
Well, I kind of, I kind of lost him.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我只是要你看着他 让他待在这间公寓
I mean, all I asked you to do was keep him in the apartment.
我知道 我知道 对不起
I know. I know. I'm sorry.
你知道吗 我想我也有错
You know what? I guess it's partially my fault, you know?
我不应该一开始就让你照顾猴子
I mean, I shouldn't have asked you to start off with a monkey.
应该先让你照看一支铅笔之类的
I should have started you off with like a pen or a pencil.
罗斯 我已经尽力了
Ross, I'm doing everything that I can.
大家都在找他 而且我还
I've got everybody looking for him and I got...
哪一位      动物控制中心
Who is it?        Animal Control.
你看 我还打电话到动物控制中心了
See, I've even got Animal Control.
你打电话给动物控制中心了
You called Animal Control?
嗯啊
Uhhuh!
怎么了 你不喜欢他们吗
Why? Do you not like them?
马塞尔是非法引进的外来动物
Marcel is an illegal exotic animal.
我是非法饲养
I'm not allowed to have him in the city.
万一被他们找到 他们就会把他带走
If they find him, they'll take him away from me.
好吧 你看 你从来没有告诉过我们这些
Okay, well now see, you never ever ever told us that.
没错 因为我没想到
That's right, because I didn't expect
你会邀请他们来这里
you were gonna invite them to the apartment.
你好 谢谢你赶过来
Hi, thanks for coming.
有人遗失猴子
Somebody called about a monkey?
噢 你知道吗
Oh,oh, you know what?
那完全是个误会
That was a complete misunderstanding.
对啊 我们以为我们养的只猴子 结果不是
Yeah, we thought we had a monkey, but we didn't.
那是顶帽子      猫
It turned out it was a hat.         Cat.
猫 我刚说的是什么
Cat. What did I say?
3楼跟4楼 我们都去看过了
Hi, we checked the third and fourth floor.
没有人看到马塞尔
No one's seen Marcel.
马塞尔
Marcel?
我叔叔马塞尔
My uncle Marcel.
噢 猴子的名字就是这样来的
Oh, is that who the monkey's named after?
好吧
Okay.
你们知道私自豢养非法引进的外来动物
Are you aware that possession of an illegal exotic
最高可罚两年牢狱
is punishable by up to two years in prison
而且动物要被没收
and confiscation of the animal.
噢 天啊
Oh my God.
你要把那个可怜的小东西关在监狱里
You'd put that poor little creature in jail?
菲比 记不记得我们说过
Pheebs, you remember how we talked about
说话前要先想一下
saying things quietly to yourself first?
记得 但不是总有时间可以这样做
Yes, but there isn't always time.
我相信一定有更友善的方式解决
Look, I'm sure there's some friendly way to reconcile this.
你先请坐
Have a seat.
我们还没自我介绍
First of all, we haven't been introduced.
我是摩妮卡盖勒
I'm Monica Geller.
噢 天啊 是你
Oh my God, you are!
而你是瑞秋葛林      对
And you're Rachel Green.         Yeah.
露伊莎基雅内蒂 林肯中学
Luisa Gianetti. Lincoln High?
每次在教室上课时 我都坐在你们后面
I sat behind you guys in homeroom.
露伊莎  噢 我的天啊
Oh! Luisa. Oh, my God.
摩妮卡  是露伊莎耶
Monica, it's Luisa!
同间教室的露伊莎
Luisa from homeroom.
太好了
Yes!
你根本不知道我是谁 对不对      不知道
You have no idea who I am, do you?         No.
完全不知道
Not at all.
也许是因为整整四年 你们都没正眼瞧过我
Well, maybe that's because you spent four years ignoring me.
说句 早安 露伊莎 或是
Would it have been so hard to say "Morning, Luisa"
好可爱的吊带裤 有那么难吗
or "Nice overalls"?
噢 真对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我不怪你
It's not so much you.
你那时候很胖 问题已经够多了
You were fat. You had your own problems.
但是你 真是个讨人厌的女生
But you, what a bitch!
什么
What?
这样好了 过去就算了
Alright, you know what? Be that as it may.
猴子的事 能不能请你帮个忙
You think you could you help us out here on that monkey thing.
就当看在过去的份上
You know, just for old times' sake?
加油 山猫队
Go Bobcats!
我可以 但是我不帮
I could. But I won't.
如果我找到猴子 他就是我的了
If I find that monkey, he's mine.
当 当 当
Dun-dun-duuuur!
很遗憾
Sorry!
马塞尔
Marcel?
马塞尔      马塞尔
Marcel?         Marcel?
嗨 有事吗
Hi, can I help you?
我们有点紧急状况
We're kind of having an emergency.
我们在找东西
And we were looking for something.
找猴子      对 你有没有看到一只猴子
A monkey.         Yes! Have you seen any?
没有 我没看到什么猴子
No. No. I haven't seen a monkey.
你们知道怎么样修理散热器吗
Do you know anything about fixing radiators?
当然 当然
Sure, sure.
你们有没有试着 把开关往相反方向转
Did you try turning the knob back the other way?
当然有      那我们就没办法了
Of course.         Oh, then, no.
你尝尝鸡尾酒 莱姆酒是不是放太多了
Taste this Daiquiri. Is there too much rum in here?
等一下 希望你们快点找到猴子
Just a second. Hope you find your monkey.
噢 不 等一下等一下
Oh, no, wait. No, no, no. Wait, wait.
我们可能不太熟悉散热器
We may not know anything about radiators per se.
但是我们对环境的冷暖
But we do have a certain amount of expertise
有一定程度的认知
in the heating and cooling milieu.
我们不是还有事情要做吗
Aren't we kind of in the middle of something here?
对 但是这些女人很热 而且需要我们帮忙
Yes, but these women are very hot and they need our help.
而且还很辣
And very hot.
我们不可以这样 好吗
We can't, all right?
很遗憾
We're sorry.
你们不知道我们有多遗憾
You have no idea how sorry.
但是我们已经答应了要去找猴子
But we promised we'd find this monkey.
如果你们看到他 他大概这么高
If you see him, he's about yea high.
叫他马塞尔他会回应
And answers to the name Marcel.
如果能够拥有你们的照片
So if we could get some pictures of you
你们就算是帮了大忙了
you'd really be helping us out.
好吧 从现在开始 你不准跟外人说话
Okay, from now on, you don't get to talk to other people.
马塞尔      马塞尔
Marcel?         Marcel!
Marcel?        Marcel?
马塞尔
Marcel?
噢 天啊      怎么了
Oh, my God!         What?!
有东西拂过我的右腿
Something just brushed up against my right leg.
那是什么
What is it?
喔 噢 没什么 那是我的左腿
Ooh! Oh, it's okay. It was just my left leg.
你看 菲比
Look, Phoebe.
噢 太好了 噢 马塞尔 过来
Oh, yeah. Oh, Marcel. Come here.
过来 马塞尔      两位小姐 请让开
Oh, come here, Marcel.         Step aside, ladies!
你要做什么
What are you gonna do?
只是一点镇静剂
Just a small tranquilizer.
快跑 马塞尔 快跑 跑啊 马塞尔
Run, Marcel! Run! Run, Marcel!
该死      你还好吧
Damn.         Are you okay?
噢 还好 应该没事
Oh, yeah! I think so.
我只是 噢
I just... Oh!
哈 哇喔
Huh. Whoah!
噢 天啊
Oh, gosh.
马塞尔      马塞尔
Marcel.        Marcel.
这太荒谬了 整个社区都找遍了
This is ridiculous. We've been all over the neighborhood.
他不见了 就这么消失了
He's gone. He's just gone.
罗斯 你怎么知道
Ross, you don't know that.
噢 拜托 现在又冷又暗
Oh come on. It's cold, it's dark.
他根本不知道路
He doesn't know the Village.
现在我的脚又受伤了
And now I have a broken foot. Oh, my...
我的猴子不见了 脚又受伤了
I have no monkey and a broken foot.
真是谢谢你
Thank you very much.
罗斯 我已经跟你道歉过无数次了
Ross you know, I've said I'm sorry like a million times.
你要我怎么做
What do you want me to do? Huh?
到底要我怎么样 要我也踢伤脚吗
What do you want? You want me to break my foot too?
好吧 我也来踢伤我的脚
Okay here, I'm gonna break my foot right now. Ow!
我的天呀 好了 这下你高兴了吧
Oh God! My God! There, are you happy now?
对 就在你踢完路标之后
Yeah, yeah. You know, now that you kicked the sign.
嘿 我突然不再想念马塞尔了
Hey, I don't miss Marcel anymore.
我又不是故意的
You know, it's not like I did this on purpose.
不 不 当然不是 这只是典型的瑞秋
No, no, no, no, no. This is just vintage Rachel.
你身边的事都是自动发生
I mean, things just sort of happen around you.
你一直都活在自己的世界里
I mean, you're off in Rachel Land
做你自己的事
doing your Rachel thing
完全无视别人的猴子
totally oblivious to people's monkeys
或是别人的感受      罗斯
or to people's feelings.        Ross.
我不想听了      罗斯
I don't even want to hear it...         Ross.
算了 可以吗      罗斯
Forget it, okay?         Ross.
怎么了 干嘛 干嘛
What? What? What?
嘿 香蕉男
Hey, banana man.
噢 真是有够强的
Oh, this is so intense.
我一边的屁股完全麻掉
One side of my butt is totally asleep.
另一边却完全不知道
And the other side has no idea.
嗨 香蕉是你买的吗
Hi, did you order some bananas?
那又怎样      猴子还我
What about it?         Give me my monkey back.
我没有猴子
I don't have a monkey.
那买那么多香蕉干什么       补钾
Then what's with all the bananas?         Potassium.
马塞尔 马塞尔
Marcel? Marcel.
他在哪儿 他在哪儿 马塞尔 马塞尔
Okay, where is he? Where is he? Marcel? Marcel?
马塞尔
Marcel！
你对他做了什么
What have you done to him?
那是我的猴子 派蒂 猴子派蒂
That's my monkey. That's Patty. Patty the monkey.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
马塞尔 快点过来      派蒂过来
Come here, Marcel. Come on.         Come here, Patty.
过来这里  马塞尔
Come here, Marcel.
派蒂 过来这里
Come here, Patty.
过来 猴子 过来这里
Here, monkey. Here, monkey. Here, monkey.
抓到了
Gotcha.
猴子还我
Okay, give me my monkey back.
他是我的猴子
That's my monkey.
你们俩到法官那儿去理论吧
You're both gonna have to take this up with the judge.
那不是我的猴子 不过裙子是我的
That's not my monkey. Just the dress is mine.
你方便的时候再寄回来给我
You can send it back whenever.
我要我的猴子      不行
All right, I want my monkey.         No.
拜托你 露伊莎
Oh, come on, Luisa.
很抱歉 舞会皇后
Sorry, prom queen.
你高中时干嘛那么讨厌
You had to be a bitch in high school.
为何不当个胖妹
You couldn't have been fat.
好吧 高中时 我是舞会皇后
Alright look, okay, in high school I was the prom queen.
也是返校日皇后和班长
And I was the homecoming queen and the class president.
而你也一直都存在
And you were also there.
如果你带走这只猴子
Look, if you take this monkey...
我会失去生命中一个最重要的人
I will lose one of the most important people in my life.
你可以恨我
You can hate me if you want.
但是请不要惩罚他
But please do not punish him.
拜托你 露伊莎 此时你有机会成为大人物
Come on, Luisa, you have a chance to be the bigger person here.
把握机会吧
Take it.
不要
No.
好吧
All right.
那我就要打电话给你的长官
Well then how about I call your supervisor.
告诉她你在我朋友的屁股上开了一枪
And I tell her that you shot my friend in the ass with a dart.
嘿 终于能把这件衣服脱下来了
Hey, it'll be nice to get this off finally,
感觉一定很好 对吧
won't it? Yes, it will.
不然继续让你穿着 也没关系
Or we can leave it on for now. That's fine.
再配上鞋
You know, with the right pair of pumps
就是完美的一套小礼服了
that would be a great little outfit.
很抱歉先前对你的态度那么差
Listen, I'm sorry I was so hard on you before.
我只是
You know, I just...
不 罗斯 别这样说
No, Ross, come on. No, no.
都是我不好 几乎让你失去...
It was my fault. I almost lost your...
不 不 多亏了你 他才能回来
No no. Yeah, but you were the one who got him back.
你真的很了不起
You know, you were great.
嘿 我们的酒还在
Hey, we still have that bottle of wine.
你还有没有心情来点 葡萄酒
Are you in the mood for something grape?
好啊 好主意
Sure, that would be good.
好
All right!
一定是邻居在吸地板
The neighbors must be vacuuming.
只要我们在这里
Well, as long as we're here...
不是在谈那个话题
and not on the subject.
我刚在想
I was thinking about
我们两个都在生对方的气
how mad we got at each other before.
我在想 可能也是因为我们都
And I was thinking maybe it was partially because of how we...
瑞秋      巴瑞
Rachel?        Barry?
我没办法 我办不到 我不能娶敏蒂
I can't.I can't do it. I can't marry Mindy.
我想我还爱着你      噢
I think I'm still in love with you.         Oh!
我们得开始锁门了
We have got to start locking that door.
那是我演"音乐之声"的时候
This is me in "The Sound of Music".
有看到冯崔普家的孩子们吗      没有
You see the Von Trapp kids?         No.
那是因为我站在他们前面
That's because I'm in front of them.
对哦 我以为那是阿尔卑斯山
Yeah, I thought that was an Alp.
中学并不是我喜欢的时光
Well, high school was not my favorite time.
是吗 我中学时超快乐的
I don't know. I loved high school, you know?
四年都在派对 约会 跟女生上床
It was just like four years of parties and dating and sex.
我则是跟四百个男生 一起上寄宿学校
Yeah well, I went to boarding school with 400 boys.
想上床 就得改变整个性向
Any sex I had would've involved a major lifestyle choice.
天啊 感觉好像是几百万年前的事了 对不对
Gosh, doesn't it seem like a million years ago?
噢
Oh!
噢 我的屁股开始苏醒了 噢
Oh, my butt cheek is waking up. Oh!
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
海盗编号：HDT19-P1-24-19-01-1212